♪ low. tense music ♪
All right. everybody hold on.
A congresswoman was kidnapped
on American soil...
- [gunfire]
- [grunts]
- [Joe] Congresswoman Hernandez?
- Yeah.
...her family killed
at the behest
of the Chinese
Ministry of State.
We'd like to get a Lioness
on the ground.
Do it.
What do you know
about the Lioness program?
- Are you a Lioness?
- I run it.
I don't know
if I can trust this girl.
But I know that I can trust you.
What's your mission now?
To protect the mission.
From everything. Including you.
We could choose not to fight.
But choosing not to fight
is how warehouses fill up
with children.
[Joe]
I took one in the field.
I'm hunting how to make peace
with walking away for you.
For them. For me.
Well. I hope you find it.
Your father's the mission now.
- Why?
- Because this is
how he survives.
- They know.
- Who's "they"?
[Josie]
CIA
Special Activities.
- [gasps]
- The mission is to show Iran
and China that we aren't the
only nation with an open border.
Do not get yourself caught.
Everyone's watching
on this one.
Am I a part of this?
You're the part.
We're gonna find out
how well you fly.
Two minutes to target.
♪ quiet music ♪
[Neal] I wasn't sure
you were coming home.
I wasn't sure I still had one
to come home to.
[Neal] You always have
one to come home to.
Look who's home!
[Charlie]
Mom? Is that you?
- [Kate] Mom?
- It's me. baby. Oh.
♪ tense. screeching music ♪
[newswoman 1]
The French government has said
it is considering all options.
including declaring
a state of emergency
after a third night
of escalating
violence and rioting...
[newsman 1] Let's start
with the Middle East.
The Times is reporting
that Hamas
has denied reports that it has
ignored requests from
the international community
concerning the crisis
in Gaza...
[newswoman 2] A devastating
scene. meanwhile. in Oaksville.
Several people dead
and even more missing
from an explosion
at an explosives plant...
[newswoman 3] Dozens of fighters
were killed in overnight
border clashes between
Pakistan and Afghanistan
in the most serious
fighting between...
[newswoman 4]
Ukraine's president said Russia
targeted the country
with 450 drones and 30 missiles
in a countrywide attack
targeting the...
[newswoman 5] Well. Max.
we've been on lockdown
here in these capitol buildings
for almost four hours now.
[newswoman 6]
ATF. TBI. Homeland Security.
and several other agencies
are currently...
[newswoman 7] The attorney
general's office in Brazil
has filed an indictment
- against 39 people...
- [newsman 2] The Middle East is
the fulcrum of it all.
we know this. But the thing
could spread like wildfire.
[newswoman 8]
...Israel remains in Gaza
and still rejects
a two-state solution.
so is this the dawn
of a new Middle East?
- [Neal] Good morning.
- Good morning.
Oh. good God.
it's freezing. [chuckles]
- It helps with inflammation.
- [Neal] Yeah.
so does Advil. honey.
I don't want a pill to do it.
I want my body to do it.
Well. I can think of a few
things I want your body to do.
That window closed
about an hour ago.
- There was a window?
- Yeah. and you missed it.
No.
[chuckles]
[music playing faintly]
I thought you finished
your homework last night.
Dad. what's the capital
of Maine?
Uh. capital. uh... Honey.
what's the capital of Maine?
Uh. Augusta.
Mm. That's Georgia.
No. the capital of Georgia's
Atlanta. honey.
She's right.
It's Augusta. Daddy.
Really? Hmm. Never heard of it.
- What about Vermont?
- Vermont. that is Burlington.
Montpelier.
- It's weird that you know that.
- [Kate] How come
- you don't know it. Dad?
- [Neal] Okay. wise guys.
who can name the key nerves
of the thoracic wall?
That's easy.
It's the intercostal nerve...
- You're disqualified.
- [girls laughing]
Why am I disqualified?
You're-you're disqualified.
[chuckles]
[Kate] Okay. wait. wait. wait.
Here's a question. Ready?
X cubed. minus 6X squared.
plus 11X. minus six equals zero.
- What?
- I didn't hear a question.
[Kate]
Okay. question.
What are the variables
that make the equation zero?
No. never in your life will that
have a practical application.
I'm pulling you
from that school.
- [laughs]
- Oh. my God. It's so easy.
- Easy? You're grounded.
- [Kate] Grounded? Really? Why?
I don't know yet.
Are you back for dinner?
I should be.
Could get used to
this nine-to-five thing.
[sighs] Don't.
See you ladies tonight.
Ah. no love for Dad?
I'm saving all my love
for you. Daddy.
- Ew! [groans]
- All right. Gross.
- Gross.
- [Joe] Okay.
- Fine. fine. fine.
- Oh. okay. All right. all right.
- [Kate] Bye. Mom. love you.
- [Charlie] Bye. Mom.
All right. all right.
Finish up. We got to go.
♪ dramatic music ♪
[birds singing]
[chuckles]
- [sighs]
- Anything interesting?
I never thought the headline
"End of Democracy"
would ring so hollow.
Can only cry "wolf"
so many times.
[sighs] Seems so shortsighted.
An entire industry
rendering itself irrelevant.
Not if you think
about how they were trained
and who trained them.
- Just follow the money.
- Yeah.
Qatar alone has donated
over $11 billion dollars
to U.S. universities.
China has donated
$2.3 billion since 2012.
with $12 billion in tuition paid
for Chinese nationals
at our universities.
And you're surprised that
graduates of those schools are
espousing communist agendas
and declaring
democracy is dying?
That's what
they were trained to say.
Doesn't scare you even a little?
Fool's gold. honey.
You want to scare me.
start talking about AI.
That's the real end
of democracy.
- [phone buzzing]
- Oh.
Hey. you on your way in?
I'll be there in 30. You?
[Meade]
Across town. security brief.
[Joe]
Am I needed?
No. not yet.
[Joe]
We're pretty close over here.
[Meade]
Well. you know the deal.
A lot of red tape
on this side of the fence.
[tires screeching]
[car honks]
- Oh. nice.
- [Meade] What's nice?
[grunts]
Shit! I'm blackjacked!
I'm blackjacked!
[Meade]
Joe?
[groans]
[screams]
[screams] Damn it! No!
[grunting]
[Meade]
Blackjack on Raven.
unfolding in real time.
Access beacon. Send all assets
to last known location.
[Joe screaming]
♪ suspenseful. dramatic music ♪
♪ dramatic. haunting music ♪
♪♪♪
♪ tense. dramatic music ♪
[security wand whistling]
Where's the park?
[Meade]
Georgetown campus.
How'd this come our way?
Approached Kyle at a bar.
- What bar?
- The Net. He thought he was
being honeypotted.
She said she saw him in Kiev
with 46 and then at
the Ukraine embassy last week.
She's FISU. worked her way
into Russia's SVR 2018.
- Long time to double agent.
- We reached out to Kiev.
- FISU verified it.
- Okay.
So what does she have?
Pretty curious
about that myself.
♪ tense. suspenseful music ♪
[panting]
We good?
You're good.
It's not how
we like to do things.
SVR watches their own
more than they watch you.
We've been looking for a way
since the war started.
An opportunity appeared.
I took it.
Okay.
What are you gonna do about it?
Aleksi Yurimov.
I'm sorry. I'm not up
on my Russian spies.
The Middle East is my theater.
- You know SSD?
- Yes.
He runs it.
He's moved to the front.
I have his location.
Okay. Yay for you.
We want you to have him.
Why would we want that?
Leverage. Maybe you trade him.
Why would you want that?
He's Putin's hammer.
If we kill him. Putin's
retaliation will be severe.
But if you take him.
it's just the game.
And a big risk to a unit
or a Ground Branch detail
that gets trotted
before the world
on their way to a gulag
if they fail.
You'd be taking Putin's queen
off the chessboard.
Do you understand the value
of that for all of us?
Oh. I understand. For you.
But what do we get in return?
- What do you want?
- I don't know. What do you do?
- What's your field?
- Recruitment and infiltration.
You know honeypot?
Mm. I know honeypot.
I hold the jar.
How do we contact you?
Give me your number.
I'll have someone con...
Not on your fucking life.
You give contact to me.
and we'll reach out. Maybe.
[Oleksandra sighs]
Only good for a week.
If we're interested.
we'll be in touch.
♪ tense. dramatic music ♪
[tires screech]
Go smooth?
- Mm. it was interesting.
- [Two Cups] Oh. yeah?
Where does "interesting"
send us?
Ever been to Ukraine?
[groans]
You got to be kidding me. boss.
Uh. you know. Ukraine is on the
bucket list there. chief-eroni.
Yeah. I think it is now.
[Bobby]
Fuck.
[Bobby sighs]
[indistinct radio chatter]
♪ tense. suspenseful music ♪
[drones buzzing]
[gunfire]
[gunfire continues]
[projectile whistles]
[explosion in distance]
[explosions continue
in distance]
[projectile whistles]
[explosions continue
in distance]
[gunfire and explosions
continue in distance]
Popping smoke.
[explosions continue
in distance]
Move.
Last man.
[explosions continue]
[gunfire continues in distance]
♪♪♪
[indistinct radio chatter]
[low. indistinct chatter]
[chatter continues]
Was a good trip?
[scoffs]
I wouldn't say that. but...
[Amber] Well. looks
like you have all your arms
and all your legs.
so I would say
it was a good trip.
Unit's in here.
[Joe sighs]
Ah. there she is.
Ain't the border. babies.
this some big boy shit
right here.
It's fucking crazy.
is what this is.
[Amber]
We suspect that Russians
have tunneled into
this gas pipeline right here.
and they're using it
to ferry troops and equipment.
Your perimeter detail
are North Koreans.
They're motivated fighters.
but their tactics are atrocious.
They're also having
limited success
linking their comms
with Russian communications.
which is something
we feel like we can exploit.
Where's the target?
Take a look at the monitor.
All right. so Russians
implant locators
in their agents.
Our mole was good enough
to give us ID coordinates
for our target.
Looks like he's lying
in a field.
He's under it.
He's in the pipeline.
Mm-hmm.
So he's a senior level agent.
- correct?
- Correct.
What's he doing in the front
with amateur protection?
Planning something.
[Amber] They used
open pipelines for their
last offensive. and it appears
that they're planning
something similar.
If he came here
with a Russian SF squadron.
we would be dumping
daisy cutters
all over that entire valley.
but he came in light.
- just like you.
- [Joe] All right.
What's the plan?
Cody.
Yeah.
Excuse me. brother.
So. we're here.
We're gonna come to here.
We will move through
the trench to their left flank.
which is Rally Point Alpha.
First we'll send
a drone swarm over.
get their heads down.
hit 'em with 105s.
155s. 120 mortars.
then we'll sic the dogs on 'em.
[laughs]
These fucking guys.
[Cody] SBU Alpha.
a Ukrainian outfit's gonna
move in from here.
They're gonna hit here
and here.
We are gonna work our way
up this trench to the LCC.
Then we'll move
on the farmhouse here.
blow the door.
put the dogs to work again.
Love their macho bullshit.
- I fucking love it.
- [Cody] And then. yeah.
it's just a footrace
to the beacon.
- Piece of cake.
- [Cody] Pretty simple.
Where are we?
You fight cover on exfil.
From where?
From right here.
[Bobby]
No. no. no. That's bullshit.
- We're her shield.
- [Two Cups] Yeah. whoa. whoa.
we go where she goes. Okay?
That ain't gonna work for us.
Who the fuck
do you think you are. sport?
Hey. don't put your hands
on my fucking teammate.
- [overlapping arguing]
- Hey!
You people have
zero fucking authority.
You ain't even
in the fucking Army.
- Fucking Army.
- Oh. that's what this is.
- an official Army op?
- Everyone dial it down.
[Cody J] Buddy.
this ain't an HRT mission.
- this is fucking war.
- [Tucker] What. you don't think
we know war? 'Cause we were
just in one with your ass
- right behind us.
- [Joe] Tucker.
She's got to have someone
from our team with her.
Great way to start an op. guys.
And you wonder why
we don't want you with us.
You're acting like
a bunch of fucking amateurs.
You've been training in
the tactics of trench warfare.
Bobby. huh?
- [Bobby sighs]
- No?
What about defense
against a drone swarm?
Been working on that?
Uh-uh. you sure have not.
You are not trained
for the tactics of this place.
Then what the fuck
are we doing here?
Brass needs CIA to PID.
This unit. they have no file.
no folders. and we're
just not gonna risk it.
DLA's not a secure
Internet source.
We have a beacon. but we
don't know what he looks like.
[Bobby]
This is bullshit.
Bush-league bullshit
- is what it is.
- You calling me
- bush-league. motherfucker?
- Bobby.
- Bobby. stand down.
- That's how you're acting.
I'm doing my fucking job.
Your job was to bring her
in country.
- and you did it.
- Fuck you.
Now your job is over.
[Kyle]
Jesus Christ. children. I'll go.
All right? I'll go.
Everybody happy?
- No. OPSEC says her.
- [Kyle] Good?
[Amber]
It has to be her.
You have your TTPs
and we have ours.
I would like to know
the men on my six.
You know me.
Cody... you know what I mean.
Cruz.
you ain't forgot everything
we taught you. Have you?
I ain't forgot shit.
There you go.
You stay on my six.
she stays on yours.
Is everybody happy now?
[Tucker]
I don't like this shit. boss.
Look. there's Tier One
and there's these fuckers.
You'll be safer with them
than you are in this bunker.
I got her.
0600 is go. All right?
There's a mist
that comes off the river.
Their junk thermals
can't see through it.
We're doing this in daylight?
They got NV just like we do.
but their thermals are dog shit.
Gen 2 at best. so...
We need the mist.
Just let us overwatch
from stage one. huh?
- SBU Alpha has overwatch.
- Why not fucking us?
Because if SBU Alpha
gets cut to shit.
it doesn't end up
on the front page
of the fucking New York Times.
Are there any more
goddamn questions?
Stay in the bunker.
We'll go through
all this again. 0400.
That means the meeting
is over. ladies.
- [Two Cups laughs]
- [Joe] Come on.
There's a room for us
across the hall.
- [Two Cups] Love it.
- [Amber] We're gonna play nice.
♪ tense. dramatic music ♪
Not you. Joe.
No. you two stay with us.
[Bobby]
Fuck this.
[Tucker]
That's some bullshit.
You know. it's not like we were
running with those fuckers
five years ago!
Running with these guys
five months ago.
[Two Cups]
Goddamn it!
Listen up.
you haven't trained for this.
I've been here a week.
[chuckles]
This fucking place.
it's like World War I
and Star Wars slammed
into each other.
You got fucking drones
and every concept weapon
on the planet being
test-driven out there
while soldiers are still
charging over trench walls
with goddamn bayonets.
[scoffs] Y-You'll see.
trust me. you'll see.
Now. I'm real fucking happy
to be sitting it out
right here in this bunker.
And mark my words.
if they snatch this fucker.
getting him out's gonna be
the real trick
'cause Russia will chase us
all the way to Poland
for the son of a bitch.
Yeah. we may miss
the fight tomorrow.
but we ain't missing the fight.
[Randy]
Fuck.
[sighs]
♪ tense. dramatic music ♪
["People Hatin'"
by The Red Clay Strays playing]
♪ Hey. people hatin' ♪
♪ You're not listening
to what I'm saying ♪
♪ I'm sick of waiting ♪
♪ All this arguing
is aggravating ♪
♪ Hey. you people hatin' ♪
- [clattering]
- ♪ You're not listening ♪
♪ To what I'm saying ♪
♪ I'm so sick of waiting ♪
♪ All this arguing
is aggravating... ♪
Morning.
Yeah.
♪ percussive. dramatic music ♪
Lock and load
if you ain't already.
We're ready.
- Everybody up?
- Yeah.
All right. here we go.
[growling]
Oh. shit.
I guess turning the dogs loose
isn't a metaphor for these guys.
[drones buzzing]
Holy shit.
This isn't a firefight
in Paktika.
- Head on a swivel. Got it?
- Copy.
[Cody] Send 'em. send 'em.
send 'em. send 'em. send 'em.
[dogs barking]
Hey. right on my fucking six.
- Do not fall behind.
- Roger that. I got you.
On me.
Go.
[shouting in Korean]
- [dogs barking]
- [soldiers screaming]
[Grady]
Titan. that'll do.
[barks]
- Grady. you up?
- We're up.
- Move.
- [dogs barking]
- [projectile whistles]
- [explosions nearby]
[grunting]
♪♪♪
- [soldiers shouting in Korean]
- [dogs barking]
[explosions continue]
[Cody over comms]
Hatchet 1. this is Sword 1.
We are inbound to release point.
Bravo. acknowledge.
[soldier over comms] Roger.
Sword 1. We're in position.
[explosions and gunfire
continue]
Incoming!
[projectiles whistle]
[both grunt]
[Cody]
Fuck.
Somebody get on this other LMG!
Not you. Get down. get down.
Whoo! I could get used
to one of these!
[Cody] All right. we're clear.
Let's move. [grunts]
What the fuck was that?!
- Hey!
- Huh? What the fuck?
There is no mission without you.
do you understand me?
Until we have the target.
you are the mission.
So keep your fucking head down.
And you. check your fire
on the exfil. all right?
- We ain't the target.
- I got you.
Yeah. I see that.
Do you hear me?
No. don't nod. Acknowledge me.
Roger. We don't shoot you.
We move. Dogs.
[barking]
[Cody]
Send 'em.
Smoke 'em.
- [dogs barking]
- [soldiers screaming]
On me.
Breacher.
Execute.
[soldiers shouting in distance]
[yells]
[dog growling]
[Grady]
Titan.
That'll do.
[Cody]
Move.
Move. move. move.
Pretty quiet
since they went to the house.
- Yep.
- [Tex] They run everything
suppressed. so even if
they are shooting...
[Bobby chuckles]
Nobody's shooting back?
[Tucker]
It is Delta.
[door opens]
Hey. you're not supposed
to be out here.
Yeah. and you're not supposed
to be in fucking Ukraine. bro.
- None of us are.
- [Tex] We don't work for you.
bud. Different branch.
- We stay here.
- [man] They have satellites
fixed on this position.
Russian SVR is staring
at you fuckers as we speak.
I don't give a shit.
We're overwatch
for their return. so fuck off.
[man] Artillery
is their overwatch. Fine.
When they swarm drones.
we lock this fucking door
and we don't open it for shit.
Hey. if we want that door open.
we're gonna open it.
And you ain't gonna fucking like
how we do it.
but I promise you it'll be open.
Motherfucker.
Breach.
[Two Cups]
Yep.
[Bobby] It's making me
real fucking nervous.
You never get nervous
about me getting shot. Bobbo.
'Cause you always
get fucking shot.
You're wasting my time.
[explosion]
[Randy]
Frags.
[Bobby]
Theirs or ours?
Uh. who can say?
Fuck.
[shells clatter]
Got one.
- Needs a medic.
- [gunshots]
We ain't got no medic for him.
Let's go.
♪ tense. suspenseful music ♪
[Cruz]
Boss?
Yep. Move.
[pulls pin]
[soldiers yelling]
- [Cody] Dogs.
- [dogs barking]
[soldiers shouting in distance]
[soldiers screaming]
[dog barks]
- [dogs barking]
- [men screaming]
[dog squeals]
[gunfire]
[whimpering]
[man screaming]
[gunfire]
[dogs growling. barking]
[Cody]
Range to beacon.
On me.
♪♪♪
Blow it.
[soldiers shouting in distance]
[man groans]
Anyone speak Russian?
[Cody]
Joe. to me.
Which one?
Gray beard right in front
of you. long hair.
[Cody]
Dump the rest.
[Aleksi grunts]
- [screaming]
- [Cody] Gun.
Oh. got a knife.
Cody. we need him fit to travel.
[Grady]
No. we need him concussed.
worried about getting
the shit kicked out of him.
- not trying to escape.
- He has to be able to walk.
If he can't walk.
we will carry him.
[Cody]
Phone.
- Tracker. where is it?
- Left armpit.
DJ.
[Aleksi groaning]
[screaming]
Got it.
[Cody]
Hey. fuck that. man.
- let him bleed.
- All right. he's good. then.
- [Aleksi groans]
- Burn him.
- Arms.
- Tie and bag.
[Cody J]
Got it.
- Ready.
- All right. up.
[Cody J]
Get him up.
[Cody]
On me.
Got him.
Walk.
All right. brother.
Got to boogie.
I'm right behind you.
[dog whimpering]
[explosions in distance]
I need you two on point.
We got it.
[Cody]
Sandman. this is Sword 1.
We are jackpot and inbound
on primary exfil break.
Fire mission. TRP. cowboys.
immediate suppression.
ten rounds. H.E. quick. over.
- [soldier] Roger that. Sword 1.
- [Cody] Okay. move.
[explosions nearby]
[Grady]
Last man.
- [projectiles whistling]
- Move. move. move.
Here they come!
Pop smoke! Pop smoke!
[garbled radio transmission]
[projectiles whistling]
[explosions in distance]
Hope we're running
the right fucking way.
Just keep running.
What the fuck?!
[male voice]
Return to base.
Soldier. return to base.
[Joe]
Run!
Never seen that shit.
Pop more smoke! More smoke!
Blind those fucking things!
[Joe]
Keep going! Come on!
Last man!
[Joe shouts indistinctly]
[Cody]
Move. Move.
Move. go. go. go. go. go. go!
- [man] Go. go. go. go. go!
- [Cody] Go. go. go. go. go.
Come on. go. go. go. go. go!
Go. go. go. go. go!
♪ somber. dramatic music ♪
CIA PID?
I confirmed.
[Grady groaning]
Son of a bitch! Goddamn it!
[Bobby]
Go smooth?
As smooth as these things go.
You got a lot of blood
on your face there.
Yeah. that's not mine.
[Cody J]
We debriefing?
No. fuck no.
Not here. we're not.
We're getting
the fuck out of here.
Have everyone
ready to move. 1800.
Hey. brother. You got to get her
ready to travel. too.
- Those motherfuckers.
- [Cody] No.
Get her ready to travel.
Them handlers is
a different breed. aren't they?
They're all a different breed.
All right. let's police up
all this shit.
Let's get the fuck out of here.
Uh. exactly how are we
gonna do that. boss?
[Joe sighs]
[sighs]
That was pretty fucking nutty
right there.
We just killed a bunch of people
for a chess piece
in a war that has nothing
to do with us.
Got something to do with us.
They got SF and CIA
all over the place.
That's what I'm trying
to wrap my head around.
It's not the place
to talk about it.
Where you going?
I have no fucking idea.
Do they have a place for us?
Across the hall. they said.
Seen a lot of crazy shit. boss.
What the hell?
Not here. Bobby.
Fucking robots and drones
and shit.
Not here.
Do we have an exfil?
Same way we came in.
just backwards.
♪ dramatic music ♪
♪♪♪
- Hey. you're home.
- I am.
- What time is it?
- It's late.
Or... early.
depending on your perspective.
- [groans] Okay.
- No. No. no. no.
Don't get up. I just wanted
to see your face.
- I'll be up in a minute.
- Okay.
- Mm. Love you.
- Bye.
[knock on door]
♪ low. suspenseful music ♪
Can I help you?
We're with state police.
Would you mind
stepping outside with us?
I would mind very much.
What is this about?
Please. step outside.
We need you to step outside.
Yeah. I'm gonna need your name.
your badge number.
your fucking watch commander.
a warrant. and all sorts of shit
I don't think
either of you assholes have.
Please. Ma'am.
Outside.
You're not the police.
but you're two minutes
from meeting them.
[groans]
[panting]
Oh. fuck.
I need FBI to my house
right now. I'm blown.
and I have two down.
♪ tense. dramatic music ♪